<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AU CRU</title>
    <link>https://au-cru.github.io/site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AU CRU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://au-cru.github.io/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://au-cru.github.io/site/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://au-cru.github.io/site/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensing and attribution</title>
      <link>https://au-cru.github.io/site/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://au-cru.github.io/site/license/</guid>
      <description>Use and re-use The website content is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License and the code is licensed under a MIT License.
This means that any content or code on this website can be used, copied, modified, and so on anywhere, as long as there is attribution.
Website The website layout was modified from a template by Bootstrapious and ported to Hugo by DevCows.
Images Images on the front page are all freely available from Unsplash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More information</title>
      <link>https://au-cru.github.io/site/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://au-cru.github.io/site/more-info/</guid>
      <description>About Vision Reproducibility, open scientific practices, and analytic transparency are increasingly being requested or required of scientists and researchers, but training on these on topics is severely lacking. Nor has the culture around sharing of code and skills, or even the recognition that these concepts are important for the health of science, dramatically changed.
Our vision is to create a community of (open) research software users at Aarhus University and the surrounding area to share, learn, and support each other, so that we may better use our tools in our research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surveys</title>
      <link>https://au-cru.github.io/site/surveys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://au-cru.github.io/site/surveys/</guid>
      <description>Help us understand what the community needs, tell us when and what you want to learn, or if you want to instruct a session!    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
